[
    {
        "question": "通じる",
        "answer": "つうじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "奥",
        "answer": "おく"
    },
    {
        "question": "適切",
        "answer": "てきせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "才能",
        "answer": "さいのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "泉",
        "answer": "いずみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "面",
        "answer": "めん"
    },
    {
        "question": "気味",
        "answer": "きみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "消費",
        "answer": "しょうひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "悪口",
        "answer": "わるくち"
    },
    {
        "question": "医療",
        "answer": "いりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方法",
        "answer": "ほうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛び出す",
        "answer": "とびだす"
    },
    {
        "question": "機械",
        "answer": "きかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "減る",
        "answer": "へる"
    },
    {
        "question": "地位",
        "answer": "ちい"
    },
    {
        "question": "位",
        "answer": "くらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "著者",
        "answer": "ちょしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "迷惑",
        "answer": "めいわく"
    },
    {
        "question": "岸",
        "answer": "きし"
    },
    {
        "question": "野",
        "answer": "の"
    },
    {
        "question": "多分",
        "answer": "たぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "住宅",
        "answer": "じゅうたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "係",
        "answer": "かかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "多少",
        "answer": "たしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "上等",
        "answer": "じょうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "罹る",
        "answer": "かかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "記事",
        "answer": "きじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不",
        "answer": "ふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ直ぐ",
        "answer": "まっすぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "飯",
        "answer": "めし"
    },
    {
        "question": "変更",
        "answer": "へんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "喉",
        "answer": "のど"
    },
    {
        "question": "我々",
        "answer": "われわれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "替える",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "湾",
        "answer": "わん"
    },
    {
        "question": "握手",
        "answer": "あくしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "国語",
        "answer": "こくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "納得",
        "answer": "なっとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "刈る",
        "answer": "かる"
    },
    {
        "question": "数",
        "answer": "かず"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲劇",
        "answer": "ひげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "合わせる",
        "answer": "あわせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "痛み",
        "answer": "いたみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "攻撃",
        "answer": "こうげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "相手",
        "answer": "あいて"
    },
    {
        "question": "作品",
        "answer": "さくひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "化粧",
        "answer": "けしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "どれ",
        "answer": "どれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒ぎ",
        "answer": "さわぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "改善",
        "answer": "かいぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "成長",
        "answer": "せいちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組む",
        "answer": "くむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "詩",
        "answer": "し"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚悟",
        "answer": "かくご"
    },
    {
        "question": "地",
        "answer": "ち"
    },
    {
        "question": "自身",
        "answer": "じしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "筋肉",
        "answer": "きんにく"
    },
    {
        "question": "最中",
        "answer": "さいちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "批判",
        "answer": "ひはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貧しい",
        "answer": "まずしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "国民",
        "answer": "こくみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "袋",
        "answer": "ふくろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "棒",
        "answer": "ぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "絵画",
        "answer": "かいが"
    },
    {
        "question": "出席",
        "answer": "しゅっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "直に",
        "answer": "じかに"
    },
    {
        "question": "見解",
        "answer": "けんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "骨折",
        "answer": "こっせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "埃",
        "answer": "ほこり"
    },
    {
        "question": "仏",
        "answer": "ほとけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "癖",
        "answer": "くせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "入学",
        "answer": "にゅうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "週",
        "answer": "しゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "宅",
        "answer": "たく"
    },
    {
        "question": "費用",
        "answer": "ひよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "回り",
        "answer": "まわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "休暇",
        "answer": "きゅうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "詩人",
        "answer": "しじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "老い",
        "answer": "おい"
    },
    {
        "question": "積もる",
        "answer": "つもる"
    },
    {
        "question": "程度",
        "answer": "ていど"
    },
    {
        "question": "大半",
        "answer": "たいはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "同様",
        "answer": "どうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "重視",
        "answer": "じゅうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "期間",
        "answer": "きかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "立派",
        "answer": "りっぱ"
    },
    {
        "question": "繋ぐ",
        "answer": "つなぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "嬉しい",
        "answer": "うれしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "態度",
        "answer": "たいど"
    },
    {
        "question": "散歩",
        "answer": "さんぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "気付く",
        "answer": "きづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠陥",
        "answer": "けっかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "支給",
        "answer": "しきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "詳しい",
        "answer": "くわしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "明ける",
        "answer": "あける"
    },
    {
        "question": "勉強",
        "answer": "べんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "木曜",
        "answer": "もくよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "分野",
        "answer": "ぶんや"
    },
    {
        "question": "知識",
        "answer": "ちしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "番",
        "answer": "ばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "ジェット機",
        "answer": "ジェットき"
    },
    {
        "question": "相続",
        "answer": "そうぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "穴",
        "answer": "あな"
    },
    {
        "question": "無料",
        "answer": "むりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "喧嘩",
        "answer": "けんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "男の人",
        "answer": "おとこのひと"
    },
    {
        "question": "空く",
        "answer": "すく"
    },
    {
        "question": "腐る",
        "answer": "くさる"
    },
    {
        "question": "増加",
        "answer": "ぞうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "正",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "途端",
        "answer": "とたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "人気",
        "answer": "にんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱帯",
        "answer": "ねったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "植物",
        "answer": "しょくぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "末",
        "answer": "すえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "極",
        "answer": "ごく"
    },
    {
        "question": "世話",
        "answer": "せわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "柄",
        "answer": "え"
    },
    {
        "question": "秘密",
        "answer": "ひみつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実験",
        "answer": "じっけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "含む",
        "answer": "ふくむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "交換",
        "answer": "こうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "小包",
        "answer": "こづつみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "似合う",
        "answer": "にあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "普段",
        "answer": "ふだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "緊張",
        "answer": "きんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "縄",
        "answer": "なわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "食料",
        "answer": "しょくりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "芽",
        "answer": "め"
    },
    {
        "question": "老人",
        "answer": "ろうじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "親友",
        "answer": "しんゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "芝生",
        "answer": "しばふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "眺める",
        "answer": "ながめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "敵",
        "answer": "てき"
    },
    {
        "question": "暖かい",
        "answer": "あたたか(い)"
    },
    {
        "question": "疑問",
        "answer": "ぎもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "貸し",
        "answer": "かし"
    },
    {
        "question": "梅雨",
        "answer": "つゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "科目",
        "answer": "かもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "世の中",
        "answer": "よのなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "莫大",
        "answer": "ばくだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "皆",
        "answer": "みんな"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛",
        "answer": "あい"
    },
    {
        "question": "指導",
        "answer": "しどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄",
        "answer": "てつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "育つ",
        "answer": "そだつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "食事",
        "answer": "しょくじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出来事",
        "answer": "できごと"
    },
    {
        "question": "褒める",
        "answer": "ほめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "列",
        "answer": "れつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "籠",
        "answer": "かご"
    },
    {
        "question": "発見",
        "answer": "はっけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "随分",
        "answer": "ずいぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "いつも",
        "answer": "いつも"
    },
    {
        "question": "芝居",
        "answer": "しばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "巣",
        "answer": "す"
    },
    {
        "question": "面倒",
        "answer": "めんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "招く",
        "answer": "まねく"
    },
    {
        "question": "激しい",
        "answer": "はげしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "及ぼす",
        "answer": "およぼす"
    },
    {
        "question": "城",
        "answer": "しろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "電子",
        "answer": "でんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "確認",
        "answer": "かくにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "知らせ",
        "answer": "しらせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "尤も",
        "answer": "もっとも"
    },
    {
        "question": "株",
        "answer": "かぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "対する",
        "answer": "たいする"
    },
    {
        "question": "失業",
        "answer": "しつぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "正式",
        "answer": "せいしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "図",
        "answer": "ず"
    },
    {
        "question": "鍵",
        "answer": "かぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "議長",
        "answer": "ぎちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "節約",
        "answer": "せつやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "日",
        "answer": "にち"
    },
    {
        "question": "区別",
        "answer": "くべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "便",
        "answer": "びん"
    },
    {
        "question": "努力",
        "answer": "どりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "素晴らしい",
        "answer": "すばらしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "見る",
        "answer": "みる"
    },
    {
        "question": "税金",
        "answer": "ぜいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "思い出",
        "answer": "おもいで"
    },
    {
        "question": "宝石",
        "answer": "ほうせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "句",
        "answer": "く"
    },
    {
        "question": "節",
        "answer": "ふし"
    },
    {
        "question": "母親",
        "answer": "ははおや"
    },
    {
        "question": "化学",
        "answer": "かがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "受け取る",
        "answer": "うけとる"
    },
    {
        "question": "清潔",
        "answer": "せいけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "帰宅",
        "answer": "きたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "販売",
        "answer": "はんばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一度に",
        "answer": "いちどに"
    },
    {
        "question": "屋根",
        "answer": "やね"
    },
    {
        "question": "監督",
        "answer": "かんとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "桜",
        "answer": "さくら"
    },
    {
        "question": "できる",
        "answer": "（可能。出現。発生）"
    },
    {
        "question": "権利",
        "answer": "けんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "加わる",
        "answer": "くわわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "神経",
        "answer": "しんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一般",
        "answer": "いっぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "徹底",
        "answer": "てってい"
    },
    {
        "question": "差",
        "answer": "さ"
    },
    {
        "question": "新た",
        "answer": "あらた"
    },
    {
        "question": "明確",
        "answer": "めいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "中心",
        "answer": "ちゅうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "雰囲気",
        "answer": "ふんいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "収穫",
        "answer": "しゅうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "議会",
        "answer": "ぎかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "計",
        "answer": "けい"
    },
    {
        "question": "実現",
        "answer": "じつげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "臭い",
        "answer": "くさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一人一人",
        "answer": "ひとりひとり"
    },
    {
        "question": "市場",
        "answer": "いちば"
    },
    {
        "question": "王",
        "answer": "おう"
    },
    {
        "question": "職",
        "answer": "しょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "会合",
        "answer": "かいごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "気候",
        "answer": "きこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "時",
        "answer": "とき"
    },
    {
        "question": "学ぶ",
        "answer": "まなぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "変化",
        "answer": "へんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "浴びる",
        "answer": "あびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "掴む",
        "answer": "つかむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "党",
        "answer": "とう"
    },
    {
        "question": "提案",
        "answer": "ていあん"
    },
    {
        "question": "値",
        "answer": "ね"
    },
    {
        "question": "主に",
        "answer": "おもに"
    },
    {
        "question": "場面",
        "answer": "ばめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "依頼",
        "answer": "いらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し訳",
        "answer": "もうしわけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全国",
        "answer": "ぜんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "陽気",
        "answer": "ようき"
    },
    {
        "question": "演技",
        "answer": "えんぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "見送り",
        "answer": "みおくり"
    },
    {
        "question": "責任",
        "answer": "せきにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "任せる",
        "answer": "まかせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "題",
        "answer": "だい"
    },
    {
        "question": "教師",
        "answer": "きょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "下り",
        "answer": "くだり"
    },
    {
        "question": "袖",
        "answer": "そで"
    },
    {
        "question": "笑い",
        "answer": "わらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "旧",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "先ず",
        "answer": "まず"
    },
    {
        "question": "取れる",
        "answer": "とれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "来",
        "answer": "らい"
    },
    {
        "question": "程",
        "answer": "ほど"
    },
    {
        "question": "土曜",
        "answer": "どよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空き",
        "answer": "あき"
    },
    {
        "question": "支出",
        "answer": "ししゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "風呂",
        "answer": "ふろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "招待",
        "answer": "しょうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "水準",
        "answer": "すいじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "硬い",
        "answer": "かたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "品",
        "answer": "しな"
    },
    {
        "question": "嵐",
        "answer": "あらし"
    },
    {
        "question": "試し",
        "answer": "ためし"
    },
    {
        "question": "方向",
        "answer": "ほうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "空",
        "answer": "から"
    },
    {
        "question": "演奏",
        "answer": "えんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "笛",
        "answer": "ふえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "元",
        "answer": "もと"
    },
    {
        "question": "鉄道",
        "answer": "てつどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "異常",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "微妙",
        "answer": "びみょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "翼",
        "answer": "つばさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "公平",
        "answer": "こうへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "申し込む",
        "answer": "もうしこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "日光",
        "answer": "にっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "役割",
        "answer": "やくわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "地方",
        "answer": "ちほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "頂上",
        "answer": "ちょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "余裕",
        "answer": "よゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "従兄弟",
        "answer": "いとこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "企業",
        "answer": "きぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "独り",
        "answer": "ひとり"
    },
    {
        "question": "冒険",
        "answer": "ぼうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "需要",
        "answer": "じゅよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "中央",
        "answer": "ちゅうおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "借金",
        "answer": "しゃっきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "辺り",
        "answer": "あたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "想像",
        "answer": "そうぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "続き",
        "answer": "つづき"
    },
    {
        "question": "制限",
        "answer": "せいげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐れる",
        "answer": "おそれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "担当",
        "answer": "たんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "重大",
        "answer": "じゅうだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "天候",
        "answer": "てんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "咳",
        "answer": "せき"
    },
    {
        "question": "現実",
        "answer": "げんじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "食物",
        "answer": "しょくもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "全然",
        "answer": "ぜんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "年月",
        "answer": "としつき"
    },
    {
        "question": "有効",
        "answer": "ゆうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "叱る",
        "answer": "しかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "劇場",
        "answer": "げきじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "金庫",
        "answer": "きんこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "余り",
        "answer": "あまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "順",
        "answer": "じゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "言語",
        "answer": "げんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "自慢",
        "answer": "じまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "気温",
        "answer": "きおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "抜く",
        "answer": "ぬく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大陸",
        "answer": "たいりく"
    },
    {
        "question": "感じる",
        "answer": "かんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "禁煙",
        "answer": "きんえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "進歩",
        "answer": "しんぽ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一方",
        "answer": "いっぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸い",
        "answer": "さいわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "加減",
        "answer": "かげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "歓迎",
        "answer": "かんげい"
    },
    {
        "question": "女王",
        "answer": "じょおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "でも",
        "answer": "でも"
    },
    {
        "question": "都市",
        "answer": "とし"
    },
    {
        "question": "原",
        "answer": "はら"
    },
    {
        "question": "様々",
        "answer": "さまざま"
    },
    {
        "question": "物音",
        "answer": "ものおと"
    },
    {
        "question": "性",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "供給",
        "answer": "きょうきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "握る",
        "answer": "にぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "管理",
        "answer": "かんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "周囲",
        "answer": "しゅうい"
    },
    {
        "question": "何",
        "answer": "なに"
    },
    {
        "question": "残り",
        "answer": "のこり"
    },
    {
        "question": "全く",
        "answer": "まったく"
    },
    {
        "question": "先日",
        "answer": "せんじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "氏",
        "answer": "し"
    },
    {
        "question": "定期",
        "answer": "ていき"
    },
    {
        "question": "税",
        "answer": "ぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "能力",
        "answer": "のうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "農業",
        "answer": "のうぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "断る",
        "answer": "ことわる"
    },
    {
        "question": "現す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "勘定",
        "answer": "かんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "酒",
        "answer": "さけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "通す",
        "answer": "とおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "香り",
        "answer": "かおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "持ち上げる",
        "answer": "もちあげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "家具",
        "answer": "かぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "現場",
        "answer": "げんば"
    },
    {
        "question": "渋滞",
        "answer": "じゅうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "就職",
        "answer": "しゅうしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "種",
        "answer": "たね"
    },
    {
        "question": "濡れる",
        "answer": "ぬれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "機嫌",
        "answer": "きげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "物事",
        "answer": "ものごと"
    },
    {
        "question": "誕生",
        "answer": "たんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "好む",
        "answer": "このむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "尊敬",
        "answer": "そんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "不足",
        "answer": "ふそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "判断",
        "answer": "はんだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "予測",
        "answer": "よそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "後者",
        "answer": "こうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "玉",
        "answer": "たま"
    },
    {
        "question": "情報",
        "answer": "じょうほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜中",
        "answer": "よなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "見舞い",
        "answer": "みまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "代金",
        "answer": "だいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "轢く",
        "answer": "ひく"
    },
    {
        "question": "博物館",
        "answer": "はくぶつかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "意思",
        "answer": "いし"
    },
    {
        "question": "滅多に",
        "answer": "めったに"
    },
    {
        "question": "象",
        "answer": "ぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "経つ",
        "answer": "たつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "観客",
        "answer": "かんきゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "汗",
        "answer": "あせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "七",
        "answer": "しち"
    },
    {
        "question": "加える",
        "answer": "くわえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "集団",
        "answer": "しゅうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "銃",
        "answer": "じゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "駄目",
        "answer": "だめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜",
        "answer": "よ"
    },
    {
        "question": "震える",
        "answer": "ふるえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "伸ばす",
        "answer": "のばす"
    },
    {
        "question": "虎",
        "answer": "とら"
    },
    {
        "question": "放送",
        "answer": "ほうそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "記念",
        "answer": "きねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "独立",
        "answer": "どくりつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出会う",
        "answer": "であう"
    },
    {
        "question": "頼る",
        "answer": "たよる"
    },
    {
        "question": "人類",
        "answer": "じんるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "最高",
        "answer": "さいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "処理",
        "answer": "しょり"
    },
    {
        "question": "婚約",
        "answer": "こんやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "守る",
        "answer": "まもる"
    },
    {
        "question": "進学",
        "answer": "しんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大",
        "answer": "だい"
    },
    {
        "question": "記憶",
        "answer": "きおく"
    },
    {
        "question": "豪華",
        "answer": "ごうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "都会",
        "answer": "とかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "理解",
        "answer": "りかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "体温",
        "answer": "たいおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "付ける",
        "answer": "つける"
    },
    {
        "question": "触れる",
        "answer": "ふれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "範囲",
        "answer": "はんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "上京",
        "answer": "じょうきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "模様",
        "answer": "もよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "幼い",
        "answer": "おさない"
    },
    {
        "question": "維持",
        "answer": "いじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "通り過ぎる",
        "answer": "とおりすぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "表面",
        "answer": "ひょうめん"
    },
    {
        "question": "丘",
        "answer": "おか"
    },
    {
        "question": "向く",
        "answer": "むく"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲",
        "answer": "なか"
    },
    {
        "question": "試す",
        "answer": "ためす"
    },
    {
        "question": "引退",
        "answer": "いんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "男子",
        "answer": "だんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "呼吸",
        "answer": "こきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "防ぐ",
        "answer": "ふせぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "疑う",
        "answer": "うたがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "賢い",
        "answer": "かしこい"
    },
    {
        "question": "命令",
        "answer": "めいれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "要するに",
        "answer": "ようするに"
    },
    {
        "question": "土地",
        "answer": "とち"
    },
    {
        "question": "眺め",
        "answer": "ながめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "灯",
        "answer": "ひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "避ける",
        "answer": "さける"
    },
    {
        "question": "救助",
        "answer": "きゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "通行",
        "answer": "つうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "追い付く",
        "answer": "おいつく"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛行",
        "answer": "ひこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "限る",
        "answer": "かぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "現れる",
        "answer": "あらわれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "幾つ",
        "answer": "いくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "犯人",
        "answer": "はんにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "時刻",
        "answer": "じこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "舌",
        "answer": "した"
    },
    {
        "question": "円",
        "answer": "えん"
    },
    {
        "question": "地平線",
        "answer": "ちへいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "義務",
        "answer": "ぎむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "完全",
        "answer": "かんぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "好み",
        "answer": "このみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "粗",
        "answer": "あら"
    },
    {
        "question": "安定",
        "answer": "あんてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦手",
        "answer": "にがて"
    },
    {
        "question": "谷",
        "answer": "たに"
    },
    {
        "question": "会計",
        "answer": "かいけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "署名",
        "answer": "しょめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "便り",
        "answer": "たより"
    },
    {
        "question": "見当",
        "answer": "けんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "精々",
        "answer": "せいぜい"
    },
    {
        "question": "友人",
        "answer": "ゆうじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "週間",
        "answer": "しゅうかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勧める",
        "answer": "すすめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "墓",
        "answer": "はか"
    },
    {
        "question": "衝突",
        "answer": "しょうとつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "婦人",
        "answer": "ふじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "額",
        "answer": "がく"
    },
    {
        "question": "立ち上がる",
        "answer": "たちあがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "しまった",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "詰める",
        "answer": "つめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "表",
        "answer": "ひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "製造",
        "answer": "せいぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "仲間",
        "answer": "なかま"
    },
    {
        "question": "観察",
        "answer": "かんさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "平等",
        "answer": "びょうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "教授",
        "answer": "きょうじゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "主張",
        "answer": "しゅちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "連想",
        "answer": "れんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "離す",
        "answer": "はなす"
    },
    {
        "question": "向ける",
        "answer": "むける"
    },
    {
        "question": "金属",
        "answer": "きんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "年寄",
        "answer": "としより"
    },
    {
        "question": "疲れ",
        "answer": "つかれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "資源",
        "answer": "しげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "誰か",
        "answer": "だれか"
    },
    {
        "question": "感心",
        "answer": "かんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "占める",
        "answer": "しめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "印象",
        "answer": "いんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "存在",
        "answer": "そんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "動かす",
        "answer": "うごかす"
    },
    {
        "question": "時期",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "手術",
        "answer": "しゅじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦しい",
        "answer": "くるしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "九",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "背",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "姿",
        "answer": "すがた"
    },
    {
        "question": "小麦",
        "answer": "こむぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "発達",
        "answer": "はったつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "何か",
        "answer": "なにか"
    },
    {
        "question": "思わず",
        "answer": "おもわず"
    },
    {
        "question": "信頼",
        "answer": "しんらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "迷子",
        "answer": "まいご"
    },
    {
        "question": "準備",
        "answer": "じゅんび"
    },
    {
        "question": "現象",
        "answer": "げんしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "骨",
        "answer": "ほね"
    },
    {
        "question": "否定",
        "answer": "ひてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "人込み",
        "answer": "ひとごみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真似",
        "answer": "まね"
    },
    {
        "question": "尻",
        "answer": "しり"
    },
    {
        "question": "贅沢",
        "answer": "ぜいたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "哲学",
        "answer": "てつがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "実行",
        "answer": "じっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "倒す",
        "answer": "たおす"
    },
    {
        "question": "主義",
        "answer": "しゅぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "逮捕",
        "answer": "たいほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大統領",
        "answer": "だいとうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "謎",
        "answer": "なぞ"
    },
    {
        "question": "裁判",
        "answer": "さいばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "通り",
        "answer": "とおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "舞台",
        "answer": "ぶたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "一時",
        "answer": "いちじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "調査",
        "answer": "ちょうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "誤り",
        "answer": "あやまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "味方",
        "answer": "みかた"
    },
    {
        "question": "瓶",
        "answer": "びん"
    },
    {
        "question": "穀物",
        "answer": "こくもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "構成",
        "answer": "こうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "悪魔",
        "answer": "あくま"
    },
    {
        "question": "克服",
        "answer": "こくふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "始まり",
        "answer": "はじまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "気の毒",
        "answer": "きのどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "十",
        "answer": "じゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "方",
        "answer": "ほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "備える",
        "answer": "そなえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "下す",
        "answer": "おろす"
    },
    {
        "question": "優秀",
        "answer": "ゆうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "囲む",
        "answer": "かこむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "関心",
        "answer": "かんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮らし",
        "answer": "くらし"
    },
    {
        "question": "中古",
        "answer": "ちゅうこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "意志",
        "answer": "いし"
    },
    {
        "question": "月",
        "answer": "つき"
    },
    {
        "question": "他",
        "answer": "た"
    },
    {
        "question": "思想",
        "answer": "しそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "有利",
        "answer": "ゆうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "作曲",
        "answer": "さっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "粉",
        "answer": "こな"
    },
    {
        "question": "川",
        "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "衣服",
        "answer": "いふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "選手",
        "answer": "せんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "絶滅",
        "answer": "ぜつめつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "年間",
        "answer": "ねんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "姉妹",
        "answer": "しまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "全て",
        "answer": "すべて"
    },
    {
        "question": "板",
        "answer": "いた"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶然",
        "answer": "ぐうぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運転",
        "answer": "うんてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "俳優",
        "answer": "はいゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "典型",
        "answer": "てんけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "助手",
        "answer": "じょしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "換える",
        "answer": "かえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "最終",
        "answer": "さいしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "永久",
        "answer": "えいきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "用心",
        "answer": "ようじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "割る",
        "answer": "わる"
    },
    {
        "question": "礼儀",
        "answer": "れいぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "兎",
        "answer": "うさぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "級",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "同時",
        "answer": "どうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "だが",
        "answer": "だが"
    },
    {
        "question": "全体",
        "answer": "ぜんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "真面目",
        "answer": "まじめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "旅",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "question": "経営",
        "answer": "けいえい"
    },
    {
        "question": "別に",
        "answer": "べつに"
    },
    {
        "question": "違いない",
        "answer": "ちがいない"
    },
    {
        "question": "明かり",
        "answer": "あかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "患者",
        "answer": "かんじゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸運",
        "answer": "こううん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勘",
        "answer": "かん"
    },
    {
        "question": "失う",
        "answer": "うしなう"
    },
    {
        "question": "流れる",
        "answer": "ながれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "犯罪",
        "answer": "はんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "問い",
        "answer": "とい"
    },
    {
        "question": "吐く",
        "answer": "はく"
    },
    {
        "question": "分析",
        "answer": "ぶんせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "ふと",
        "answer": "（副）"
    },
    {
        "question": "許可",
        "answer": "きょか"
    },
    {
        "question": "身長",
        "answer": "しんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "同一",
        "answer": "どういつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "活気",
        "answer": "かっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "豊富",
        "answer": "ほうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "土産",
        "answer": "みやげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "微笑む",
        "answer": "ほほえむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "意識",
        "answer": "いしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "国会",
        "answer": "こっかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "過ごす",
        "answer": "すごす"
    },
    {
        "question": "既に",
        "answer": "すでに"
    },
    {
        "question": "梅",
        "answer": "うめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "狂う",
        "answer": "くるう"
    },
    {
        "question": "画家",
        "answer": "がか"
    },
    {
        "question": "型",
        "answer": "かた"
    },
    {
        "question": "利益",
        "answer": "りえき"
    },
    {
        "question": "環境",
        "answer": "かんきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "労働",
        "answer": "ろうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "入院",
        "answer": "にゅういん"
    },
    {
        "question": "預ける",
        "answer": "あずける"
    },
    {
        "question": "大会",
        "answer": "たいかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "衛星",
        "answer": "えいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "正直",
        "answer": "しょうじき"
    },
    {
        "question": "貰う",
        "answer": "もらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "根",
        "answer": "ね"
    },
    {
        "question": "邪魔",
        "answer": "じゃま"
    },
    {
        "question": "感情",
        "answer": "かんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "金",
        "answer": "かね"
    },
    {
        "question": "嘘",
        "answer": "うそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "劣る",
        "answer": "おとる"
    },
    {
        "question": "個人",
        "answer": "こじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "独特",
        "answer": "どくとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "批評",
        "answer": "ひひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不可",
        "answer": "ふか"
    },
    {
        "question": "脇",
        "answer": "わき"
    },
    {
        "question": "祭",
        "answer": "まつり"
    },
    {
        "question": "吸収",
        "answer": "きゅうしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "張る",
        "answer": "はる"
    },
    {
        "question": "留める",
        "answer": "とめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "畑",
        "answer": "はたけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "提出",
        "answer": "ていしゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不正",
        "answer": "ふせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "溺れる",
        "answer": "おぼれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "注",
        "answer": "ちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "地下",
        "answer": "ちか"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛情",
        "answer": "あいじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一体",
        "answer": "いったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦い",
        "answer": "たたかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦しむ",
        "answer": "くるしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "数字",
        "answer": "すうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "家賃",
        "answer": "やちん"
    },
    {
        "question": "今日",
        "answer": "こんにち"
    },
    {
        "question": "涙",
        "answer": "なみだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "当てる",
        "answer": "あてる"
    },
    {
        "question": "合図",
        "answer": "あいず"
    },
    {
        "question": "可",
        "answer": "か"
    },
    {
        "question": "拍手",
        "answer": "はくしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不平",
        "answer": "ふへい"
    },
    {
        "question": "内容",
        "answer": "ないよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "煙",
        "answer": "けむり"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠点",
        "answer": "けってん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文句",
        "answer": "もんく"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚ます",
        "answer": "さます"
    },
    {
        "question": "目標",
        "answer": "もくひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "破産",
        "answer": "はさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "観光",
        "answer": "かんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "床",
        "answer": "ゆか"
    },
    {
        "question": "格好",
        "answer": "かっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "光景",
        "answer": "こうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "毛布",
        "answer": "もうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大した",
        "answer": "たいした"
    },
    {
        "question": "急に",
        "answer": "きゅうに"
    },
    {
        "question": "現在",
        "answer": "げんざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "料金",
        "answer": "りょうきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "転ぶ",
        "answer": "ころぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "故障",
        "answer": "こしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日本",
        "answer": "にっぽん"
    },
    {
        "question": "満ちる",
        "answer": "みちる"
    },
    {
        "question": "考慮",
        "answer": "こうりょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "隠す",
        "answer": "かくす"
    },
    {
        "question": "未だ",
        "answer": "まだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "性格",
        "answer": "せいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "論じる",
        "answer": "ろんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "だから",
        "answer": "だから"
    },
    {
        "question": "歌手",
        "answer": "かしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "挨拶",
        "answer": "あいさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "計る",
        "answer": "はかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦痛",
        "answer": "くつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "前進",
        "answer": "ぜんしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "事実",
        "answer": "じじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "弁当",
        "answer": "べんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "苦労",
        "answer": "くろう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掃除",
        "answer": "そうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "昼食",
        "answer": "ちゅうしょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "食糧",
        "answer": "しょくりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "彼等",
        "answer": "かれら"
    },
    {
        "question": "食欲",
        "answer": "しょくよく"
    },
    {
        "question": "動詞",
        "answer": "どうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "単語",
        "answer": "たんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "解ける",
        "answer": "とける"
    },
    {
        "question": "鼠",
        "answer": "ねずみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自動",
        "answer": "じどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "巨大",
        "answer": "きょだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "特徴",
        "answer": "とくちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "地域",
        "answer": "ちいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "訳",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "以来",
        "answer": "いらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "降ろす",
        "answer": "おろす"
    },
    {
        "question": "再び",
        "answer": "ふたたび"
    },
    {
        "question": "酸素",
        "answer": "さんそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "扱う",
        "answer": "あつかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "解決",
        "answer": "かいけつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "手品",
        "answer": "てじな"
    },
    {
        "question": "営業",
        "answer": "えいぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "平均",
        "answer": "へいきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "穏やか",
        "answer": "おだやか"
    },
    {
        "question": "角",
        "answer": "すみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "信じる",
        "answer": "しんじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "都",
        "answer": "みやこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "二十",
        "answer": "はたち"
    },
    {
        "question": "幅",
        "answer": "はば"
    },
    {
        "question": "作家",
        "answer": "さっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "引っ張る",
        "answer": "ひっぱる"
    },
    {
        "question": "回す",
        "answer": "まわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "質",
        "answer": "しつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "急速",
        "answer": "きゅうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "価値",
        "answer": "かち"
    },
    {
        "question": "指す",
        "answer": "さす"
    },
    {
        "question": "幕",
        "answer": "まく"
    },
    {
        "question": "正確",
        "answer": "せいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "生まれ",
        "answer": "うまれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "心配",
        "answer": "しんぱい"
    },
    {
        "question": "高速",
        "answer": "こうそく"
    },
    {
        "question": "金額",
        "answer": "きんがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "終える",
        "answer": "おえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "農家",
        "answer": "のうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "強力",
        "answer": "きょうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "通学",
        "answer": "つうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "大抵",
        "answer": "たいてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "混雑",
        "answer": "こんざつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "月曜",
        "answer": "げつよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "支払う",
        "answer": "しはらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "下さる",
        "answer": "くださる"
    },
    {
        "question": "底",
        "answer": "そこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "音",
        "answer": "おん"
    },
    {
        "question": "保存",
        "answer": "ほぞん"
    },
    {
        "question": "主要",
        "answer": "しゅよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "帯",
        "answer": "おび"
    },
    {
        "question": "共通",
        "answer": "きょうつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "楽",
        "answer": "らく"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬",
        "answer": "うま"
    },
    {
        "question": "作物",
        "answer": "さくもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不利",
        "answer": "ふり"
    },
    {
        "question": "大気",
        "answer": "たいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "腰",
        "answer": "こし"
    },
    {
        "question": "基づく",
        "answer": "もとづく"
    },
    {
        "question": "知事",
        "answer": "ちじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "胃",
        "answer": "い"
    },
    {
        "question": "身",
        "answer": "み"
    },
    {
        "question": "岩",
        "answer": "いわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "素",
        "answer": "もと"
    },
    {
        "question": "横断",
        "answer": "おうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "皿",
        "answer": "さら"
    },
    {
        "question": "組合",
        "answer": "くみあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "全員",
        "answer": "ぜんいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "御",
        "answer": "お"
    },
    {
        "question": "手間",
        "answer": "てま"
    },
    {
        "question": "注文",
        "answer": "ちゅうもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生物",
        "answer": "せいぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "信仰",
        "answer": "しんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "医師",
        "answer": "いし"
    },
    {
        "question": "世間",
        "answer": "せけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "行儀",
        "answer": "ぎょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "事情",
        "answer": "じじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "河",
        "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "損害",
        "answer": "そんがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "頬",
        "answer": "ほほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "文",
        "answer": "ぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "非常",
        "answer": "ひじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "適する",
        "answer": "てきする"
    },
    {
        "question": "弾",
        "answer": "たま"
    },
    {
        "question": "閉じる",
        "answer": "とじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "損",
        "answer": "そん"
    },
    {
        "question": "稼ぐ",
        "answer": "かせぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中",
        "answer": "ちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "砂漠",
        "answer": "さばく"
    },
    {
        "question": "商人",
        "answer": "しょうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "負け",
        "answer": "まけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮らす",
        "answer": "くらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "混乱",
        "answer": "こんらん"
    },
    {
        "question": "実施",
        "answer": "じっし"
    },
    {
        "question": "外す",
        "answer": "はずす"
    },
    {
        "question": "今に",
        "answer": "いまに"
    },
    {
        "question": "増す",
        "answer": "ます"
    },
    {
        "question": "戻す",
        "answer": "もどす"
    },
    {
        "question": "無視",
        "answer": "むし"
    },
    {
        "question": "礼",
        "answer": "れい"
    },
    {
        "question": "順調",
        "answer": "じゅんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "傷",
        "answer": "きず"
    },
    {
        "question": "効く",
        "answer": "きく"
    },
    {
        "question": "率",
        "answer": "りつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "速度",
        "answer": "そくど"
    },
    {
        "question": "影響",
        "answer": "えいきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "居眠り",
        "answer": "いねむり"
    },
    {
        "question": "大戦",
        "answer": "たいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "利口",
        "answer": "りこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掲示",
        "answer": "けいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "縦",
        "answer": "たて"
    },
    {
        "question": "布",
        "answer": "ぬの"
    },
    {
        "question": "役",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "地球",
        "answer": "ちきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "居る",
        "answer": "おる"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱心",
        "answer": "ねっしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "成功",
        "answer": "せいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐怖",
        "answer": "きょうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "劇",
        "answer": "げき"
    },
    {
        "question": "要素",
        "answer": "ようそ"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗せる",
        "answer": "のせる"
    },
    {
        "question": "明らか",
        "answer": "あきらか"
    },
    {
        "question": "流行",
        "answer": "りゅうこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "注ぐ",
        "answer": "そそぐ"
    },
    {
        "question": "基",
        "answer": "もと"
    },
    {
        "question": "未来",
        "answer": "みらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "後",
        "answer": "うしろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "省く",
        "answer": "はぶく"
    },
    {
        "question": "感じ",
        "answer": "かんじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "学習",
        "answer": "がくしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "出身",
        "answer": "しゅっしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "不満",
        "answer": "ふまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "理想",
        "answer": "りそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "冷静",
        "answer": "れいせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "芸術",
        "answer": "げいじゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "保証",
        "answer": "ほしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結ぶ",
        "answer": "むすぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "章",
        "answer": "しょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "流す",
        "answer": "ながす"
    },
    {
        "question": "残す",
        "answer": "のこす"
    },
    {
        "question": "撃つ",
        "answer": "うつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "心理",
        "answer": "しんり"
    },
    {
        "question": "生き物",
        "answer": "いきもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "過去",
        "answer": "かこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "左右",
        "answer": "さゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "委員",
        "answer": "いいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "繰り返す",
        "answer": "くりかえす"
    },
    {
        "question": "人生",
        "answer": "じんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "祝う",
        "answer": "いわう"
    },
    {
        "question": "反抗",
        "answer": "はんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "移動",
        "answer": "いどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "捕まる",
        "answer": "つかまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "故郷",
        "answer": "こきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お昼",
        "answer": "おひる"
    },
    {
        "question": "手伝い",
        "answer": "てつだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "生地",
        "answer": "きじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宿",
        "answer": "やど"
    },
    {
        "question": "用いる",
        "answer": "もちいる"
    },
    {
        "question": "論文",
        "answer": "ろんぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運動",
        "answer": "うんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "差別",
        "answer": "さべつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "金曜",
        "answer": "きんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "輪",
        "answer": "わ"
    },
    {
        "question": "承知",
        "answer": "しょうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "設備",
        "answer": "せつび"
    },
    {
        "question": "勿論",
        "answer": "もちろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "包み",
        "answer": "つつみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "付き合い",
        "answer": "つきあい"
    },
    {
        "question": "審判",
        "answer": "しんぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "悲しむ",
        "answer": "かなしむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "友",
        "answer": "とも"
    },
    {
        "question": "貯金",
        "answer": "ちょきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "虫歯",
        "answer": "むしば"
    },
    {
        "question": "方々",
        "answer": "かたがた"
    },
    {
        "question": "確かめる",
        "answer": "たしかめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "振る",
        "answer": "ふる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鎖",
        "answer": "くさり"
    },
    {
        "question": "務め",
        "answer": "つとめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "外",
        "answer": "ほか"
    },
    {
        "question": "広告",
        "answer": "こうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "真剣",
        "answer": "しんけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "追う",
        "answer": "おう"
    },
    {
        "question": "誤解",
        "answer": "ごかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "参加",
        "answer": "さんか"
    },
    {
        "question": "宜しい",
        "answer": "よろしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "失望",
        "answer": "しつぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "活動",
        "answer": "かつどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "切れる",
        "answer": "きれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "塀",
        "answer": "へい"
    },
    {
        "question": "主婦",
        "answer": "しゅふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "感謝",
        "answer": "かんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸出",
        "answer": "ゆしゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "平和",
        "answer": "へいわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "僅か",
        "answer": "わずか"
    },
    {
        "question": "裸",
        "answer": "はだか"
    },
    {
        "question": "講演",
        "answer": "こうえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "財産",
        "answer": "ざいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸せ",
        "answer": "しあわせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "地区",
        "answer": "ちく"
    },
    {
        "question": "端",
        "answer": "はし"
    },
    {
        "question": "登山",
        "answer": "とざん"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠席",
        "answer": "けっせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "議論",
        "answer": "ぎろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "誘う",
        "answer": "さそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "命じる",
        "answer": "めいじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "予算",
        "answer": "よさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "商売",
        "answer": "しょうばい"
    },
    {
        "question": "祝い",
        "answer": "いわい"
    },
    {
        "question": "回復",
        "answer": "かいふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "爆発",
        "answer": "ばくはつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "案",
        "answer": "あん"
    },
    {
        "question": "比較",
        "answer": "ひかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "下",
        "answer": "げ"
    },
    {
        "question": "航空",
        "answer": "こうくう"
    },
    {
        "question": "届く",
        "answer": "とどく"
    },
    {
        "question": "条件",
        "answer": "じょうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "食品",
        "answer": "しょくひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "結局",
        "answer": "けっきょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "少年",
        "answer": "しょうねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "牛",
        "answer": "うし"
    },
    {
        "question": "濠",
        "answer": "ほり"
    },
    {
        "question": "伺う",
        "answer": "うかがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "実際",
        "answer": "じっさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "望む",
        "answer": "のぞむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "承認",
        "answer": "しょうにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "期待",
        "answer": "きたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "いえ",
        "answer": "いえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "大部分",
        "answer": "だいぶぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "札",
        "answer": "さつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "名",
        "answer": "な"
    },
    {
        "question": "通過",
        "answer": "つうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "喜び",
        "answer": "よろこび"
    },
    {
        "question": "油",
        "answer": "あぶら"
    },
    {
        "question": "景気",
        "answer": "けいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "歩道",
        "answer": "ほどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "泥",
        "answer": "どろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "求める",
        "answer": "もとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "実",
        "answer": "み"
    },
    {
        "question": "上",
        "answer": "うわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "免許",
        "answer": "めんきょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "身体",
        "answer": "しんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "夕べ",
        "answer": "ゆうべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "言う",
        "answer": "ゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日中",
        "answer": "にっちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "乗客",
        "answer": "じょうきゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "燃える",
        "answer": "もえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "違い",
        "answer": "ちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "向かい",
        "answer": "むかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "石炭",
        "answer": "せきたん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勝ち",
        "answer": "かち"
    },
    {
        "question": "現代",
        "answer": "げんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "栄養",
        "answer": "えいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "太陽",
        "answer": "たいよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "釣",
        "answer": "つり"
    },
    {
        "question": "離れる",
        "answer": "はなれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "遅刻",
        "answer": "ちこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "目的",
        "answer": "もくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "作業",
        "answer": "さぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "話し合う",
        "answer": "はなしあう"
    },
    {
        "question": "事",
        "answer": "こと"
    },
    {
        "question": "服装",
        "answer": "ふくそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "船",
        "answer": "ふね"
    },
    {
        "question": "肌",
        "answer": "はだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "汚染",
        "answer": "おせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "本人",
        "answer": "ほんにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "進める",
        "answer": "すすめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "度",
        "answer": "たび"
    },
    {
        "question": "奇妙",
        "answer": "きみょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "職業",
        "answer": "しょくぎょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "その",
        "answer": "その"
    },
    {
        "question": "全",
        "answer": "ぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "新鮮",
        "answer": "しんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "見事",
        "answer": "みごと"
    },
    {
        "question": "書斎",
        "answer": "しょさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "証明",
        "answer": "しょうめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "別れ",
        "answer": "わかれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "真っ赤",
        "answer": "まっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "注目",
        "answer": "ちゅうもく"
    },
    {
        "question": "夜明け",
        "answer": "よあけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "国家",
        "answer": "こっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "予報",
        "answer": "よほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "相当",
        "answer": "そうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "刑事",
        "answer": "けいじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "法",
        "answer": "ほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "当時",
        "answer": "とうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "近代",
        "answer": "きんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "恋人",
        "answer": "こいびと"
    },
    {
        "question": "宝",
        "answer": "たから"
    },
    {
        "question": "強調",
        "answer": "きょうちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "居間",
        "answer": "いま"
    },
    {
        "question": "羽",
        "answer": "はね"
    },
    {
        "question": "単純",
        "answer": "たんじゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "健康",
        "answer": "けんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "応じる",
        "answer": "おうじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "金持ち",
        "answer": "かねもち"
    },
    {
        "question": "密",
        "answer": "みつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "家事",
        "answer": "かじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "髪の毛",
        "answer": "かみのけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "頂く",
        "answer": "いただく"
    },
    {
        "question": "様子",
        "answer": "ようす"
    },
    {
        "question": "結果",
        "answer": "けっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "県",
        "answer": "けん"
    },
    {
        "question": "精神",
        "answer": "せいしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一家",
        "answer": "いっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "四",
        "answer": "し"
    },
    {
        "question": "暮れ",
        "answer": "くれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "しまう",
        "answer": "（終わる）"
    },
    {
        "question": "女子",
        "answer": "じょし"
    },
    {
        "question": "援助",
        "answer": "えんじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "跡",
        "answer": "あと"
    },
    {
        "question": "突然",
        "answer": "とつぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "終",
        "answer": "おわり"
    },
    {
        "question": "更に",
        "answer": "さらに"
    },
    {
        "question": "本当",
        "answer": "ほんと"
    },
    {
        "question": "支払",
        "answer": "しはらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "順番",
        "answer": "じゅんばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "得る",
        "answer": "える"
    },
    {
        "question": "州",
        "answer": "しゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "境",
        "answer": "さかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "学期",
        "answer": "がっき"
    },
    {
        "question": "王子",
        "answer": "おうじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "止す",
        "answer": "よす"
    },
    {
        "question": "温度",
        "answer": "おんど"
    },
    {
        "question": "哀れ",
        "answer": "あわれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "少女",
        "answer": "しょうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "感覚",
        "answer": "かんかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "罪",
        "answer": "つみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "正午",
        "answer": "しょうご"
    },
    {
        "question": "騒音",
        "answer": "そうおん"
    },
    {
        "question": "郵便",
        "answer": "ゆうびん"
    },
    {
        "question": "黒板",
        "answer": "こくばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "履く",
        "answer": "はく"
    },
    {
        "question": "贈る",
        "answer": "おくる"
    },
    {
        "question": "単に",
        "answer": "たんに"
    },
    {
        "question": "器用",
        "answer": "きよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "相談",
        "answer": "そうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "被る",
        "answer": "かぶる"
    },
    {
        "question": "松",
        "answer": "まつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "段",
        "answer": "だん"
    },
    {
        "question": "発表",
        "answer": "はっぴょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "実は",
        "answer": "じつは"
    },
    {
        "question": "善",
        "answer": "ぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "当たる",
        "answer": "あたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "助ける",
        "answer": "たすける"
    },
    {
        "question": "はあ",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "給料",
        "answer": "きゅうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "大臣",
        "answer": "だいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "支える",
        "answer": "ささえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "設計",
        "answer": "せっけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "嫁",
        "answer": "よめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "済ませる",
        "answer": "すませる"
    },
    {
        "question": "住民",
        "answer": "じゅうみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "回",
        "answer": "かい"
    },
    {
        "question": "すみません",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "他人",
        "answer": "たにん"
    },
    {
        "question": "筋",
        "answer": "すじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "女優",
        "answer": "じょゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "様",
        "answer": "よう"
    },
    {
        "question": "収める",
        "answer": "おさめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "硬貨",
        "answer": "こうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "請求",
        "answer": "せいきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "政府",
        "answer": "せいふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "国境",
        "answer": "こっきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "雷",
        "answer": "かみなり"
    },
    {
        "question": "最も",
        "answer": "もっとも"
    },
    {
        "question": "曜日",
        "answer": "ようび"
    },
    {
        "question": "通信",
        "answer": "つうしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "永遠",
        "answer": "えいえん"
    },
    {
        "question": "練習",
        "answer": "れんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "迎え",
        "answer": "むかえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "死亡",
        "answer": "しぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "辛い",
        "answer": "つらい"
    },
    {
        "question": "譲る",
        "answer": "ゆずる"
    },
    {
        "question": "鬼",
        "answer": "おに"
    },
    {
        "question": "泡",
        "answer": "あわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "必死",
        "answer": "ひっし"
    },
    {
        "question": "対",
        "answer": "たい"
    },
    {
        "question": "有能",
        "answer": "ゆうのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組織",
        "answer": "そしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "秒",
        "answer": "びょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "炎",
        "answer": "ほのお"
    },
    {
        "question": "禁止",
        "answer": "きんし"
    },
    {
        "question": "拡大",
        "answer": "かくだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "猿",
        "answer": "さる"
    },
    {
        "question": "常に",
        "answer": "つねに"
    },
    {
        "question": "従う",
        "answer": "したがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "予防",
        "answer": "よぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一層",
        "answer": "いっそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "技師",
        "answer": "ぎし"
    },
    {
        "question": "尊重",
        "answer": "そんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "優勝",
        "answer": "ゆうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "次第",
        "answer": "しだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "述べる",
        "answer": "のべる"
    },
    {
        "question": "流れ",
        "answer": "ながれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "操作",
        "answer": "そうさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "建築",
        "answer": "けんちく"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆",
        "answer": "ぎゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "会",
        "answer": "かい"
    },
    {
        "question": "黙る",
        "answer": "だまる"
    },
    {
        "question": "うまい",
        "answer": "うまい"
    },
    {
        "question": "椅子",
        "answer": "いす"
    },
    {
        "question": "外出",
        "answer": "がいしゅつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "外交",
        "answer": "がいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "刀",
        "answer": "かたな"
    },
    {
        "question": "自然",
        "answer": "しぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "論争",
        "answer": "ろんそう"
    },
    {
        "question": "隠れる",
        "answer": "かくれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "減らす",
        "answer": "へらす"
    },
    {
        "question": "膝",
        "answer": "ひざ"
    },
    {
        "question": "叫ぶ",
        "answer": "さけぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "症状",
        "answer": "しょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "警告",
        "answer": "けいこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "泳ぎ",
        "answer": "およぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "発明",
        "answer": "はつめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "物価",
        "answer": "ぶっか"
    },
    {
        "question": "行動",
        "answer": "こうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "立場",
        "answer": "たちば"
    },
    {
        "question": "要点",
        "answer": "ようてん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遠慮",
        "answer": "えんりょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "中学",
        "answer": "ちゅうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "資本",
        "answer": "しほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "装置",
        "answer": "そうち"
    },
    {
        "question": "発行",
        "answer": "はっこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お腹",
        "answer": "おなか"
    },
    {
        "question": "就く",
        "answer": "つく"
    },
    {
        "question": "等しい",
        "answer": "ひとしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "恩",
        "answer": "おん"
    },
    {
        "question": "留学",
        "answer": "りゅうがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "息",
        "answer": "いき"
    },
    {
        "question": "万一",
        "answer": "まんいち"
    },
    {
        "question": "束",
        "answer": "たば"
    },
    {
        "question": "勤め",
        "answer": "つとめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "入場",
        "answer": "にゅうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "陰",
        "answer": "かげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "代表",
        "answer": "だいひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "発展",
        "answer": "はってん"
    },
    {
        "question": "前者",
        "answer": "ぜんしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "専攻",
        "answer": "せんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "答案",
        "answer": "とうあん"
    },
    {
        "question": "日常",
        "answer": "にちじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "解く",
        "answer": "とく"
    },
    {
        "question": "容易",
        "answer": "ようい"
    },
    {
        "question": "考え",
        "answer": "かんがえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "明後日",
        "answer": "みょうごにち"
    },
    {
        "question": "半ば",
        "answer": "なかば"
    },
    {
        "question": "敬意",
        "answer": "けいい"
    },
    {
        "question": "直ちに",
        "answer": "ただちに"
    },
    {
        "question": "訴える",
        "answer": "うったえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "紐",
        "answer": "ひも"
    },
    {
        "question": "語",
        "answer": "ご"
    },
    {
        "question": "雇う",
        "answer": "やとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "図書",
        "answer": "としょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "とん",
        "answer": "（1000"
    },
    {
        "question": "推薦",
        "answer": "すいせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "使用",
        "answer": "しよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "直接",
        "answer": "ちょくせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "出版",
        "answer": "しゅっぱん"
    },
    {
        "question": "慎重",
        "answer": "しんちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "意外",
        "answer": "いがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "波",
        "answer": "なみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "酔う",
        "answer": "よう"
    },
    {
        "question": "お互い",
        "answer": "おたがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "数える",
        "answer": "かぞえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "食卓",
        "answer": "しょくたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "書類",
        "answer": "しょるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "厄介",
        "answer": "やっかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "博士",
        "answer": "はかせ"
    },
    {
        "question": "世紀",
        "answer": "せいき"
    },
    {
        "question": "救う",
        "answer": "すくう"
    },
    {
        "question": "刺激",
        "answer": "しげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "寄付",
        "answer": "きふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "投票",
        "answer": "とうひょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "候補",
        "answer": "こうほ"
    },
    {
        "question": "解釈",
        "answer": "かいしゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "魅力",
        "answer": "みりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "凍る",
        "answer": "こおる"
    },
    {
        "question": "餌",
        "answer": "えさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "被害",
        "answer": "ひがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "交際",
        "answer": "こうさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "大変",
        "answer": "たいへん"
    },
    {
        "question": "一種",
        "answer": "いっしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "異なる",
        "answer": "ことなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "球",
        "answer": "きゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "配達",
        "answer": "はいたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "共に",
        "answer": "ともに"
    },
    {
        "question": "双子",
        "answer": "ふたご"
    },
    {
        "question": "賛成",
        "answer": "Uӣ[い"
    },
    {
        "question": "決心",
        "answer": "けっしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "沈む",
        "answer": "しずむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "頃",
        "answer": "ころ"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫人",
        "answer": "ふじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "昨",
        "answer": "さく"
    },
    {
        "question": "一生",
        "answer": "いっしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "我慢",
        "answer": "がまん"
    },
    {
        "question": "到着",
        "answer": "とうちゃく"
    },
    {
        "question": "連続",
        "answer": "れんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "学",
        "answer": "がく"
    },
    {
        "question": "描く",
        "answer": "えがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "農民",
        "answer": "のうみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "丸",
        "answer": "まる"
    },
    {
        "question": "何とか",
        "answer": "なんとか"
    },
    {
        "question": "調子",
        "answer": "ちょうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "沖",
        "answer": "おき"
    },
    {
        "question": "余分",
        "answer": "よぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "適用",
        "answer": "てきよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "完成",
        "answer": "かんせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "報告",
        "answer": "ほうこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "出来るだけ",
        "answer": "できるだけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "位置",
        "answer": "いち"
    },
    {
        "question": "すると",
        "answer": "すると"
    },
    {
        "question": "次々",
        "answer": "つぎつぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "実に",
        "answer": "じつに"
    },
    {
        "question": "濃い",
        "answer": "こい"
    },
    {
        "question": "知恵",
        "answer": "ちえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "文明",
        "answer": "ぶんめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "代理",
        "answer": "だいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "ね",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "愉快",
        "answer": "ゆかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "語学",
        "answer": "ごがく"
    },
    {
        "question": "辞める",
        "answer": "やめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "値段",
        "answer": "ねだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "道路",
        "answer": "どうろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "貴重",
        "answer": "きちょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "叩く",
        "answer": "たたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "茶",
        "answer": "ちゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "教科書",
        "answer": "きょうかしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一言",
        "answer": "ひとこと"
    },
    {
        "question": "陸",
        "answer": "りく"
    },
    {
        "question": "困難",
        "answer": "こんなん"
    },
    {
        "question": "首相",
        "answer": "しゅしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "海外",
        "answer": "かいがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "課",
        "answer": "か"
    },
    {
        "question": "常識",
        "answer": "じょうしき"
    },
    {
        "question": "飛ばす",
        "answer": "とばす"
    },
    {
        "question": "頭痛",
        "answer": "ずつう"
    },
    {
        "question": "与える",
        "answer": "あたえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "無事",
        "answer": "ぶじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "毒",
        "answer": "どく"
    },
    {
        "question": "抱く",
        "answer": "いだく"
    },
    {
        "question": "覆う",
        "answer": "おおう"
    },
    {
        "question": "唯",
        "answer": "ただ"
    },
    {
        "question": "部分",
        "answer": "ぶぶん"
    },
    {
        "question": "遂に",
        "answer": "ついに"
    },
    {
        "question": "願う",
        "answer": "ねがう"
    },
    {
        "question": "少々",
        "answer": "しょうしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "賞",
        "answer": "しょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "笑顔",
        "answer": "えがお"
    },
    {
        "question": "商品",
        "answer": "しょうひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "文字",
        "answer": "もじ"
    },
    {
        "question": "金融",
        "answer": "きんゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "年齢",
        "answer": "ねんれい"
    },
    {
        "question": "親しい",
        "answer": "したしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "収入",
        "answer": "しゅうにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "名人",
        "answer": "めいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "そう",
        "answer": "そう"
    },
    {
        "question": "越える",
        "answer": "こえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "計画",
        "answer": "けいかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "障害",
        "answer": "しょうがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "そこ",
        "answer": "そこ"
    },
    {
        "question": "打つ",
        "answer": "ぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "検討",
        "answer": "けんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "恐ろしい",
        "answer": "おそろしい"
    },
    {
        "question": "例",
        "answer": "れい"
    },
    {
        "question": "怠ける",
        "answer": "なまける"
    },
    {
        "question": "しまい",
        "answer": "（終わり）"
    },
    {
        "question": "近頃",
        "answer": "ちかごろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "現れ",
        "answer": "あらわれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "長期",
        "answer": "ちょうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶々",
        "answer": "たまたま"
    },
    {
        "question": "友情",
        "answer": "ゆうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "合格",
        "answer": "ごうかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "選択",
        "answer": "せんたく"
    },
    {
        "question": "分",
        "answer": "ぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "違反",
        "answer": "いはん"
    },
    {
        "question": "経験",
        "answer": "けいけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "よろしく",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "除く",
        "answer": "のぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "退屈",
        "answer": "たいくつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "共同",
        "answer": "きょうどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "内",
        "answer": "うち"
    },
    {
        "question": "小",
        "answer": "しょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "合計",
        "answer": "ごうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "集中",
        "answer": "しゅうちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "組",
        "answer": "くみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "飽きる",
        "answer": "あきる"
    },
    {
        "question": "競技",
        "answer": "きょうぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "軍",
        "answer": "ぐん"
    },
    {
        "question": "為る",
        "answer": "する"
    },
    {
        "question": "券",
        "answer": "けん"
    },
    {
        "question": "者",
        "answer": "もの"
    },
    {
        "question": "等",
        "answer": "など"
    },
    {
        "question": "寧ろ",
        "answer": "むしろ"
    },
    {
        "question": "重要",
        "answer": "じゅうよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "構う",
        "answer": "かまう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人工",
        "answer": "じんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "生命",
        "answer": "せいめい"
    },
    {
        "question": "記入",
        "answer": "きにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "印",
        "answer": "しるし"
    },
    {
        "question": "表す",
        "answer": "あらわす"
    },
    {
        "question": "学者",
        "answer": "がくしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "塵",
        "answer": "ごみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "訪問",
        "answer": "ほうもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "強盗",
        "answer": "ごうとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "物理",
        "answer": "ぶつり"
    },
    {
        "question": "価格",
        "answer": "かかく"
    },
    {
        "question": "修正",
        "answer": "しゅうせい"
    },
    {
        "question": "式",
        "answer": "しき"
    },
    {
        "question": "感動",
        "answer": "かんどう"
    },
    {
        "question": "越す",
        "answer": "こす"
    },
    {
        "question": "恋",
        "answer": "こい"
    },
    {
        "question": "表現",
        "answer": "ひょうげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "修理",
        "answer": "しゅうり"
    },
    {
        "question": "間",
        "answer": "ま"
    },
    {
        "question": "状況",
        "answer": "じょうきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "粗末",
        "answer": "そまつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "罰する",
        "answer": "ばっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "連れ",
        "answer": "つれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "昇る",
        "answer": "のぼる"
    },
    {
        "question": "縁",
        "answer": "ふち"
    },
    {
        "question": "有る",
        "answer": "ある"
    },
    {
        "question": "起こる",
        "answer": "おこる"
    },
    {
        "question": "局",
        "answer": "きょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "氷",
        "answer": "こおり"
    },
    {
        "question": "売れる",
        "answer": "うれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "年中",
        "answer": "ねんじゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "事件",
        "answer": "じけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "願い",
        "answer": "ねがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "案内",
        "answer": "あんない"
    },
    {
        "question": "幾ら",
        "answer": "いくら"
    },
    {
        "question": "放す",
        "answer": "はなす"
    },
    {
        "question": "今回",
        "answer": "こんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "支店",
        "answer": "してん"
    },
    {
        "question": "影",
        "answer": "かげ"
    },
    {
        "question": "気に入る",
        "answer": "きにいる"
    },
    {
        "question": "深刻",
        "answer": "しんこく"
    },
    {
        "question": "道徳",
        "answer": "どうとく"
    },
    {
        "question": "殺す",
        "answer": "ころす"
    },
    {
        "question": "旗",
        "answer": "はた"
    },
    {
        "question": "鍋",
        "answer": "なべ"
    },
    {
        "question": "以前",
        "answer": "いぜん"
    },
    {
        "question": "土",
        "answer": "つち"
    },
    {
        "question": "責める",
        "answer": "せめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "豆",
        "answer": "まめ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宗教",
        "answer": "しゅうきょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "停留所",
        "answer": "ていりゅうじょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "切れ",
        "answer": "きれ"
    },
    {
        "question": "現金",
        "answer": "げんきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "制度",
        "answer": "せいど"
    },
    {
        "question": "同僚",
        "answer": "どうりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "発車",
        "answer": "はっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "吠える",
        "answer": "ほえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "会員",
        "answer": "かいいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "街",
        "answer": "まち"
    },
    {
        "question": "事務",
        "answer": "じむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "抱える",
        "answer": "かかえる"
    },
    {
        "question": "管",
        "answer": "くだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "書物",
        "answer": "しょもつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "決まり",
        "answer": "きまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "うん",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "間違い",
        "answer": "まちがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "取り上げる",
        "answer": "とりあげる"
    },
    {
        "question": "風景",
        "answer": "ふうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "信号",
        "answer": "しんごう"
    },
    {
        "question": "望み",
        "answer": "のぞみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "冗談",
        "answer": "じょうだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "訓練",
        "answer": "くんれん"
    },
    {
        "question": "生産",
        "answer": "せいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "優れる",
        "answer": "すぐれる"
    },
    {
        "question": "話題",
        "answer": "わだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "奪う",
        "answer": "うばう"
    },
    {
        "question": "是非",
        "answer": "ぜひ"
    },
    {
        "question": "愛する",
        "answer": "あいする"
    },
    {
        "question": "盛り",
        "answer": "さかり"
    },
    {
        "question": "大いに",
        "answer": "おおいに"
    },
    {
        "question": "貢献",
        "answer": "こうけん"
    },
    {
        "question": "積極的",
        "answer": "せっきょくてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "熱中",
        "answer": "ねっちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "憲法",
        "answer": "けんぽう"
    },
    {
        "question": "議員",
        "answer": "ぎいん"
    },
    {
        "question": "手段",
        "answer": "しゅだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "王様",
        "answer": "おうさま"
    },
    {
        "question": "機関",
        "answer": "きかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "座席",
        "answer": "ざせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "怪我",
        "answer": "けが"
    },
    {
        "question": "筆",
        "answer": "ふで"
    },
    {
        "question": "検査",
        "answer": "けんさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "台",
        "answer": "だい"
    },
    {
        "question": "お目に掛かる",
        "answer": "おめにかかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "出発",
        "answer": "しゅっぱつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "魚",
        "answer": "うお"
    },
    {
        "question": "缶",
        "answer": "かん"
    },
    {
        "question": "今後",
        "answer": "こんご"
    },
    {
        "question": "機能",
        "answer": "きのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "訓",
        "answer": "くん"
    },
    {
        "question": "無",
        "answer": "ぶ"
    },
    {
        "question": "覚める",
        "answer": "さめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "抜ける",
        "answer": "ぬける"
    },
    {
        "question": "諦める",
        "answer": "あきらめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "神",
        "answer": "かみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "独身",
        "answer": "どくしん"
    },
    {
        "question": "本物",
        "answer": "ほんもの"
    },
    {
        "question": "延期",
        "answer": "えんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "孫",
        "answer": "まご"
    },
    {
        "question": "事態",
        "answer": "じたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "体育",
        "answer": "たいいく"
    },
    {
        "question": "豊か",
        "answer": "ゆたか"
    },
    {
        "question": "必ずしも",
        "answer": "かならずしも"
    },
    {
        "question": "塔",
        "answer": "とう"
    },
    {
        "question": "幸福",
        "answer": "こうふく"
    },
    {
        "question": "腹",
        "answer": "はら"
    },
    {
        "question": "量",
        "answer": "りょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "可能",
        "answer": "かのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "生じる",
        "answer": "しょうじる"
    },
    {
        "question": "生",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "父親",
        "answer": "ちちおや"
    },
    {
        "question": "整理",
        "answer": "せいり"
    },
    {
        "question": "宇宙",
        "answer": "うちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "日曜",
        "answer": "にちよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "適度",
        "answer": "てきど"
    },
    {
        "question": "至る",
        "answer": "いたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "具体",
        "answer": "ぐたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "温暖",
        "answer": "おんだん"
    },
    {
        "question": "日付",
        "answer": "ひづけ"
    },
    {
        "question": "天然",
        "answer": "てんねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "運",
        "answer": "うん"
    },
    {
        "question": "害",
        "answer": "がい"
    },
    {
        "question": "誇り",
        "answer": "ほこり"
    },
    {
        "question": "霜",
        "answer": "しも"
    },
    {
        "question": "肩",
        "answer": "かた"
    },
    {
        "question": "対象",
        "answer": "たいしょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "絶対",
        "answer": "ぜったい"
    },
    {
        "question": "何でも",
        "answer": "なんでも"
    },
    {
        "question": "能",
        "answer": "のう"
    },
    {
        "question": "鋭い",
        "answer": "するどい"
    },
    {
        "question": "灰",
        "answer": "はい"
    },
    {
        "question": "武器",
        "answer": "ぶき"
    },
    {
        "question": "得意",
        "answer": "とくい"
    },
    {
        "question": "行き",
        "answer": "いき"
    },
    {
        "question": "団体",
        "answer": "だんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "暗記",
        "answer": "あんき"
    },
    {
        "question": "満足",
        "answer": "まんぞく"
    },
    {
        "question": "瞬間",
        "answer": "しゅんかん"
    },
    {
        "question": "示す",
        "answer": "しめす"
    },
    {
        "question": "休憩",
        "answer": "きゅうけい"
    },
    {
        "question": "偉大",
        "answer": "いだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "妙",
        "answer": "みょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "裏切る",
        "answer": "うらぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "出会い",
        "answer": "であい"
    },
    {
        "question": "記録",
        "answer": "きろく"
    },
    {
        "question": "認める",
        "answer": "みとめる"
    },
    {
        "question": "物質",
        "answer": "ぶっしつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "自殺",
        "answer": "じさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "青年",
        "answer": "せいねん"
    },
    {
        "question": "関する",
        "answer": "かんする"
    },
    {
        "question": "平ら",
        "answer": "たいら"
    },
    {
        "question": "今にも",
        "answer": "いまにも"
    },
    {
        "question": "諺",
        "answer": "ことわざ"
    },
    {
        "question": "命",
        "answer": "いのち"
    },
    {
        "question": "又",
        "answer": "また"
    },
    {
        "question": "去る",
        "answer": "さる"
    },
    {
        "question": "予期",
        "answer": "よき"
    },
    {
        "question": "曇",
        "answer": "くもり"
    },
    {
        "question": "引用",
        "answer": "いんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "約",
        "answer": "やく"
    },
    {
        "question": "不幸",
        "answer": "ふこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "伝統",
        "answer": "でんとう"
    },
    {
        "question": "針",
        "answer": "はり"
    },
    {
        "question": "経由",
        "answer": "けいゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "美人",
        "answer": "びじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "否",
        "answer": "いや"
    },
    {
        "question": "勇気",
        "answer": "ゆうき"
    },
    {
        "question": "製品",
        "answer": "せいひん"
    },
    {
        "question": "大家",
        "answer": "おおや"
    },
    {
        "question": "人物",
        "answer": "じんぶつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "少しも",
        "answer": "すこしも"
    },
    {
        "question": "分ける",
        "answer": "わける"
    },
    {
        "question": "基本",
        "answer": "きほん"
    },
    {
        "question": "田",
        "answer": "た"
    },
    {
        "question": "計算",
        "answer": "けいさん"
    },
    {
        "question": "開始",
        "answer": "かいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "知能",
        "answer": "ちのう"
    },
    {
        "question": "完了",
        "answer": "かんりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "結論",
        "answer": "けつろん"
    },
    {
        "question": "広がる",
        "answer": "ひろがる"
    },
    {
        "question": "離婚",
        "answer": "りこん"
    },
    {
        "question": "どう",
        "answer": "（接。副）"
    },
    {
        "question": "単なる",
        "answer": "たんなる"
    },
    {
        "question": "綿",
        "answer": "めん"
    },
    {
        "question": "読み",
        "answer": "よみ"
    },
    {
        "question": "互い",
        "answer": "たがい"
    },
    {
        "question": "睡眠",
        "answer": "すいみん"
    },
    {
        "question": "快適",
        "answer": "かいてき"
    },
    {
        "question": "消防",
        "answer": "しょうぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "ノー",
        "answer": "（no）"
    },
    {
        "question": "馬鹿",
        "answer": "ばか"
    },
    {
        "question": "匂い",
        "answer": "におい"
    },
    {
        "question": "移す",
        "answer": "うつす"
    },
    {
        "question": "参考",
        "answer": "さんこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "年代",
        "answer": "ねんだい"
    },
    {
        "question": "小屋",
        "answer": "こや"
    },
    {
        "question": "戦う",
        "answer": "たたかう"
    },
    {
        "question": "場",
        "answer": "ば"
    },
    {
        "question": "状態",
        "answer": "じょうたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "心臓",
        "answer": "しんぞう"
    },
    {
        "question": "一致",
        "answer": "いっち"
    },
    {
        "question": "親戚",
        "answer": "しんせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "抵抗",
        "answer": "ていこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "稲",
        "answer": "いね"
    },
    {
        "question": "診察",
        "answer": "しんさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "一番",
        "answer": "いちばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "勢い",
        "answer": "いきおい"
    },
    {
        "question": "はい",
        "answer": "（感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "確実",
        "answer": "かくじつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "印刷",
        "answer": "いんさつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "悩む",
        "answer": "なやむ"
    },
    {
        "question": "希望",
        "answer": "きぼう"
    },
    {
        "question": "輸入",
        "answer": "ゆにゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "活用",
        "answer": "かつよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "逆らう",
        "answer": "さからう"
    },
    {
        "question": "徹夜",
        "answer": "てつや"
    },
    {
        "question": "働き",
        "answer": "はたらき"
    },
    {
        "question": "信用",
        "answer": "しんよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "掛かる",
        "answer": "かかる"
    },
    {
        "question": "伸びる",
        "answer": "のびる"
    },
    {
        "question": "唯一",
        "answer": "ゆいいつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "側",
        "answer": "そば"
    },
    {
        "question": "傾向",
        "answer": "けいこう"
    },
    {
        "question": "工場",
        "answer": "こうば"
    },
    {
        "question": "両替",
        "answer": "りょうがえ"
    },
    {
        "question": "評判",
        "answer": "ひょうばん"
    },
    {
        "question": "関連",
        "answer": "かんれん"
    },
    {
        "question": "契約",
        "answer": "けいやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "夢中",
        "answer": "むちゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "不思議",
        "answer": "ふしぎ"
    },
    {
        "question": "最低",
        "answer": "さいてい"
    },
    {
        "question": "首都",
        "answer": "しゅと"
    },
    {
        "question": "評価",
        "answer": "ひょうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "この",
        "answer": "この"
    },
    {
        "question": "上達",
        "answer": "じょうたつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "記者",
        "answer": "きしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "許す",
        "answer": "ゆるす"
    },
    {
        "question": "限界",
        "answer": "げんかい"
    },
    {
        "question": "偶",
        "answer": "たま"
    },
    {
        "question": "際",
        "answer": "さい"
    },
    {
        "question": "横切る",
        "answer": "よこぎる"
    },
    {
        "question": "成績",
        "answer": "せいせき"
    },
    {
        "question": "石油",
        "answer": "せきゆ"
    },
    {
        "question": "胸",
        "answer": "むね"
    },
    {
        "question": "何で",
        "answer": "なんで"
    },
    {
        "question": "嫌う",
        "answer": "きらう"
    },
    {
        "question": "奨学金",
        "answer": "しょうがくきん"
    },
    {
        "question": "霧",
        "answer": "きり"
    },
    {
        "question": "支度",
        "answer": "したく"
    },
    {
        "question": "火災",
        "answer": "かさい"
    },
    {
        "question": "無駄",
        "answer": "むだ"
    },
    {
        "question": "要求",
        "answer": "ようきゅう"
    },
    {
        "question": "物語",
        "answer": "ものがたり"
    },
    {
        "question": "成る",
        "answer": "なる"
    },
    {
        "question": "高価",
        "answer": "こうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "金銭",
        "answer": "きんせん"
    },
    {
        "question": "大使",
        "answer": "たいし"
    },
    {
        "question": "ここ",
        "answer": "ここ"
    },
    {
        "question": "或",
        "answer": "ある"
    },
    {
        "question": "達する",
        "answer": "たっする"
    },
    {
        "question": "材料",
        "answer": "ざいりょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "中止",
        "answer": "ちゅうし"
    },
    {
        "question": "皮",
        "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "不自由",
        "answer": "ふじゆう"
    },
    {
        "question": "では",
        "answer": "では"
    },
    {
        "question": "無し",
        "answer": "なし"
    },
    {
        "question": "火曜",
        "answer": "かよう"
    },
    {
        "question": "欠ける",
        "answer": "かける"
    },
    {
        "question": "飼う",
        "answer": "かう"
    },
    {
        "question": "言わば",
        "answer": "いわば"
    },
    {
        "question": "直",
        "answer": "じき"
    },
    {
        "question": "支配",
        "answer": "しはい"
    },
    {
        "question": "現状",
        "answer": "げんじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "駐車",
        "answer": "ちゅうしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "銀",
        "answer": "ぎん"
    },
    {
        "question": "したがって",
        "answer": "したがって"
    },
    {
        "question": "一瞬",
        "answer": "いっしゅん"
    },
    {
        "question": "列車",
        "answer": "れっしゃ"
    },
    {
        "question": "軍隊",
        "answer": "ぐんたい"
    },
    {
        "question": "所為",
        "answer": "せい"
    },
    {
        "question": "それ",
        "answer": "（接。感）"
    },
    {
        "question": "成人",
        "answer": "せいじん"
    },
    {
        "question": "集まり",
        "answer": "あつまり"
    },
    {
        "question": "輝く",
        "answer": "かがやく"
    },
    {
        "question": "菓子",
        "answer": "かし"
    },
    {
        "question": "不安",
        "answer": "ふあん"
    },
    {
        "question": "噂",
        "answer": "うわさ"
    },
    {
        "question": "協力",
        "answer": "きょうりょく"
    },
    {
        "question": "革",
        "answer": "かわ"
    },
    {
        "question": "読書",
        "answer": "どくしょ"
    },
    {
        "question": "丸い",
        "answer": "まるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "建設",
        "answer": "けんせつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "表情",
        "answer": "ひょうじょう"
    },
    {
        "question": "種類",
        "answer": "しゅるい"
    },
    {
        "question": "単位",
        "answer": "たんい"
    },
    {
        "question": "徐々に",
        "answer": "じょじょに"
    },
    {
        "question": "滞在",
        "answer": "たいざい"
    },
    {
        "question": "破る",
        "answer": "やぶる"
    },
    {
        "question": "食う",
        "answer": "くう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人間",
        "answer": "にんげん"
    },
    {
        "question": "効果",
        "answer": "こうか"
    },
    {
        "question": "決定",
        "answer": "けってい"
    },
    {
        "question": "作法",
        "answer": "さほう"
    },
    {
        "question": "人種",
        "answer": "じんしゅ"
    },
    {
        "question": "宿泊",
        "answer": "しゅくはく"
    },
    {
        "question": "軒",
        "answer": "けん"
    },
    {
        "question": "急激",
        "answer": "きゅうげき"
    },
    {
        "question": "夫婦",
        "answer": "ふうふ"
    },
    {
        "question": "語る",
        "answer": "かたる"
    },
    {
        "question": "学問",
        "answer": "がくもん"
    },
    {
        "question": "演説",
        "answer": "えんぜつ"
    },
    {
        "question": "説",
        "answer": "せつ"
    }
]